A Guide to the Loudoun County (Va.) Deed Books, 1757-1785
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Loudoun County (Va.) Deed Books, 1757-1785
Library of Virginia
1146642-1146651
10 vols. (4078 p.) photostatic pages
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Use microfilm copies, Loudoun County, Reels 1-6.
Acquisition Information
These items came to the Library of Virginia in a transfer of court papers from Loudoun County.
Historical Information
Loudoun County was formed in 1757 from Fairfax County.
Scope and Content
Deed Books, 1757-1785, of Loudoun County Court. The deed books record the name of the grantor and grantee, the residence of both individuals and the description of property being sold or transferred. All of the volumes have indexes except A and L. The indexes contains the first and last names of both parties. It is arranged alphabetically from A-Z.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
Additional Loudoun County Deed Book Records can be found on microfilm at the Library of Virginia. See A Guide to County and City Records on microfilm at www.lva.lib.va.us/whatwehave/local/local_rec/index.htm
Access Terms
Loudoun County (Va.). Circuit Court.; Loudoun County (Va.)--History--18th century.; Deed books--Virginia--Loudoun County.; Land records--Virginia--Loudoun County.; Local government records--Virginia--Loudoun County.
Contents List
- Deed Book, A. 1757-1760, 1146642
- Deed Book, B. 1760-1761, 1146643
- Deed Book, D., Pt. 1 1763-1765, 1146644
- Deed Book, D., Pt. 2 1763-1765, 1146645
- Deed Book, F. 1764-1768, 1146646
- Deed Book, G. 1768-1770, 1146647
- Deed Book, I. 1771-1773, 1146648
- Deed Book, L. 1775-1778, 1146649
- Deed Book, M. 1778-1779, 1146650
- Deed Book, O. 1784-1785, 1146651